psychologistworld.com 2012-05-27

# Contact Information - Psychologist World

| 

**  Psychologist World**  
  
---  
  
**  Browse by Category:**  
  
| 

**Behavioral Psychology**  
Approach, Aversion Therapy, Conditioning, Flooding, more...  
  
---  
  
**Biological Approach**  
Approach, Brain Explorer, Biology & Behavior, Lobotomy, Narcotics, more...  
  
**Body Language**  
Reading Body Language, Truth Signals, Non-Verbal Signals, Self Image, more...  
  
**Cognitive Psychology**  
Cognitive Approach, more...  
  
**Developmental Psychology**

Developmental Overview, Attachments  
  
**Disorders (Mental)**  
Depression, OCD, Narcolepsy, Phobias, PTSD, Schizophrenia, Synesthesia, more...  
  
**Dreams**  
Interpret Your Dreams Guide, Dream Symbols, Nightmares, Why do we dream?, more...  
  
**Emotion**

Attraction, Emotion Guide, Love, Types of Love, Anxiety, Jealousy, Narcissism, Pride Emotion, Self Pity Emotion, Vanity Emotion, more...  
  
**Freud**  
Sigmund Freud, Evaluation, Free Association, Personality Type Test, Psychosexual theory, more...  
  
**Humanistic Approach**  
Approach Overview  
  
**Memory**   
Association, Conditioning, Rehersal, Levels of Processing, Flashbulb Memory, Forgetting, Memory Improvement, Working Memory Model, more...  
  
******Personality**  
Conforming in Groups, Authority, Brainwashing, Influence of Language, Social Influence, more...  
  
**Sleep**  
Sleep Deprivation, Sleeping Disorders, Stages of Sleep, more...  
  
**Stress**  
What is Stress?, Anger Test, Fight or Flight Response, Karoshi, Stress Management, Stress Test, more...   
  
**Personality Tests**  
Are you Fixated?, Personality Type Test, Anger Test, Stress, Depression & Anxiety Test, more...  
  
**View all articles...**  
  
**  Site Information: **  
  
Contact Details & Privacy Policy - Psychologist World

> **UK Customer Support & Sales: **(01302) 786977
> 
> **International Customer Support & Sales:** +44 (1302) 786977
> 
> **Alternative You can write to the Psychologist World Head Office at:**
> 
> 78 Tennyson Avenue
> 
> Doncaster
> 
> South Yorkshire
> 
> DN5 8EX
> 
> England
> 
> **Email: support psychologistworld.com**

##### Privacy Policy

###### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or Practitioner details. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use 'cookies' to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'Do we use cookies' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
• To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
• To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
• To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

• To send periodic emails

###### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers databases to be only accessed as stated above.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to maintain subscriptions.

###### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

###### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, unless we provide you with advanced notice. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Data is processed and stored in the EU and in some cases, countries outside of the EU including but not limited to the United States of America.

###### Third party links

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

###### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

###### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

>  

In line with most major web sites, this site uses cookies to enable users to use specific functions on the website, and to track usage of the site.

###### What data is stored in cookies?

This site uses cookies to store statistics about a user's visit so that we can improve the site's usability, and to store essential user-specific information such as login details and the items that you add to your shopping basket. This site assumes implied consent with regards to a user’s request to save a setting (e.g. country, login details, shopping cart change), and where cookies are automatically set, this is in compliance with our Terms and Conditions of use.

###### What cookies are used to store information?

This site uses cookies to store statistics about a user’s visit so that we can improve the site’s usability, and to store essential user-specific information such as login details and the items that you add to your shopping basket.

  * __utma   
Third party-set Google Analytics cookie. Used to track user clicks on the website to improve the site. 
  * __utmb   
Third party-set Google Analytics cookie.  Statistics pertaining to a user’s visit. 
  * __utmc  
Third party-set Google Analytics cookie.  Time spend on site. 
  * __utmz   
Third party-set Google Analytics cookie. Source by which user found the site. 
  * aa  
e.g. login  
Login information required to enable subscribers to log in.
  * bb  
e.g. 098f6bcd4621d373cade4e832627b4f6  
Login information required to enable subscribers to log in.
  * Other Product Cookies:   
Used to track users for purposes such as Google AdWords and Analytics.
  * Other cookies:   
e.g. Login details, information for administrating users  
These cookies shouldn’t affect general visitors.

###### How can I prevent my web browser from storing cookies?

The most effective way to prevent this site and 3rd parties such as Google from storing cookies is to block the domains of the cookies (e.g. “.hypnoticworld.com”) in your web browser settings. This varies between browser brands and versions. You can find more information below:

Microsoft®  Windows® users:  
<http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies>

FireFox users:  
<http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Blocking%20cookies>

Safari users:  
<http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/3.0/en/9277.html>

Users of other web browsers can usually find information from the manufacturer of the software, usually through the Help section of the program.

For more information on our cookies policy, please contact us – email support details can be found on the Contact Us page.

###### Self Hypnosis CD's from Hypnotic World:

###### Keep Up-to-Date:

###### Sign Up for Full Access:

Access hundreds of theories, approaches, study and experiment overviews, plus a range of psychology guides. Sign Up

|  |   |   
---|---|---  
  | 

**More in this area:**

|    
 | 

Behavioral Psychology  
Biological Psychology  
Body Language Reading  
Cognitive Psychology  
Developmental Psychology  
Dreams  
Emotions  
Freudian Psychology  
Influence & Personality Psychology  
Memory  
Personality Tests  
Psychology Issues  
Sleep Psychology  
Stress Management  

|  |    
|   |   
|
